<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bicycle and Dimed</title>
    <description>On (Not) Getting By on the Right in America.</description>
    <link>http://timesize.site/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://timesize.site/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 12:57:27 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 12:57:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meetups</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a new post about meetups.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 12:57:27 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://timesize.site/meetups</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://timesize.site/meetups</guid>
        
        
        <category>meetups</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Subhuman Window Treatment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I delivered to a posh? building in uptown Oakland, with an awkwardly positioned intercom. I lament encountering those things. They feel like ancestors to LED watches, side by side with the mobile device that makes this platform possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The box, of course, did not work as planned and as an occupant approached I struggled to stay out of the way as she oddly needed to tag the side of the speaker-box perpendicular to her doorway in order to enter. I then spun the other way to allow a another women through. This apparently didn’t leave the normal amount of room for her husband to open the door from the angle he’s accustomed to. He abruptly suggested I, “Let [him] around ‘dude’.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t remind him I’m a human even though I’m working, and not for him I’d add, because his wife was pushing a stroller. For a moment I assumed I had blocked her way. Quite pleasantly I was surprised by the woman offering a “please” as the word he was looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This altercation likely came about because I made the fatal mistake of mentioning the service I work for instead of merely using my name at the door. I am clearly not an associate of a neighbor, and so ought to tap dance around occupants as I magically appear at and apartment door without seating foot in the hall.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 08:45:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://timesize.site/SubhumanWindowTreatment</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://timesize.site/SubhumanWindowTreatment</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Psych Lane</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Guy honking and insisting for me to get off of the designated bike lane that not every street even has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Told him I am literally exactly where I’m supposed to be as we stopped at the same sign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were on a street with a yellow dotted line but he thought that I should get completely off of my lane instead of him just passing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://timesize.site/PsychLane</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://timesize.site/PsychLane</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reserved Cheats</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This b!tch says you are welcome to me while removing herself from the bike parking spot in the BART train. From the plants herself in the disabled seat immediately thereafter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Old maybe but senior citizen I doubt.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://timesize.site/ReservedCheats</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://timesize.site/ReservedCheats</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
